const questions = [
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this Egyptian player played for Liverpool and totalled 23 Goals and  13 Assists.",
        answer: "Mohamed Salah"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this South Korean player played for Tottenham and totalled 23 Goals and 7 Assists.",
        answer: "Son Heung-min"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this English player played for Tottenham and totalled 17 Goals and 9 Assists.",
        answer: "Harry Kane"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this Belgian player played for Manchester City and totalled 15 Goals and 8 Assists.",
        answer: "Kevin De Bruyne"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this English player played for West Ham and totalled 12 Goals and 10 Assists.",
        answer: "Jarrod Bowen"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this English player played for Chelsea and totalled 11 Goals and 10 Assists.",
        answer: "Mason Mount"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this Portuguese player played for Manchester Utd and totalled 18 Goals and 3 Assists.",
        answer: "Cristiano Ronaldo"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this English player played for Leicester City and totalled 12 Goals and 8 Assists.",
        answer: "James Maddison"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this Portuguese player played for Liverpool and totalled 15 Goals and 4 Assists.",
        answer: "Diogo Jota"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this Jamaican player played for West Ham and totalled 10 Goals and 8 Assists.",
        answer: "Michail Antonio"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this Senegalese player played for Liverpool and totalled 16 Goals and 2 Assists.",
        answer: "Sadio Mané"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this English player played for Arsenal and totalled 11 Goals and 7 Assists.",
        answer: "Bukayo Saka"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this English player played for Manchester City and totalled 13 Goals and 5 Assists.",
        answer: "Raheem Sterling"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this English player played for Brentford and totalled 12 Goals and 5 Assists.",
        answer: "Ivan Toney"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this English player played for Leicester City and totalled 15 Goals and 2 Assists.",
        answer: "Jamie Vardy"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this English player played for Leicester City and totalled 6 Goals and 10 Assists.",
        answer: "Harvey Barnes"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this Nigerian player played for Watford and totalled 10 Goals and 6 Assists.",
        answer: "Emmanuel Dennis"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this Portuguese player played for Manchester United and totalled 10 Goals and 6 Assists.",
        answer: "Bruno Fernandes"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this Brazilian player played for Manchester City and totalled 8 Goals and 8 Assists.",
        answer: "Gabriel Jesus"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this Algerian player played for Manchester City and totalled 11 Goals and 5 Assists.",
        answer: "Riyad Mahrez"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this Brazilian player played for Everton and totalled 10 Goals and 5 Assists.",
        answer: "Richarlison"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this English player played for Southampton and totalled 10 Goals and 5 Assists.",
        answer: "James Ward-Prowse"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this Ivorian player played for Crystal Palace and totalled 14 Goals and 1 Assist.",
        answer: "Wilfried Zaha"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this English player played for Liverpool and totalled 2 Goals and 12 Assists.",
        answer: "Trent Alexander-Arnold"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this Algerian player played for West Ham and totalled 8 Goals and 6 Assists.",
        answer: "Saïd Benrahma"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this English player played for Manchester City and totalled 9 Goals and 5 Assists.",
        answer: "Phil Foden"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this English player played for Chelsea and totalled 5 Goals and 9 Assists.",
        answer: "Reece James"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this Finnish player played for Norwich City and totalled 11 Goals and 3 Assists.",
        answer: "Teemu Pukki"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this Brazilian player played for Leeds United and totalled 11 Goals and 3 Assists.",
        answer: "Raphinha"
    },
    {
        question: "In 2021-22, this English player played for Aston Villa and totalled 7 Goals and 6 Assists.",
        answer: "Danny Ings"
    }
];

const EPLPlayerQuestions = questions.sort(() => Math.random() - 0.5)

export default EPLPlayerQuestions;